
--- ppt/slides/slide1.xml ---
International Friendship Day 2026! | Singapore: Forging Friendships in a Complex World

--- ppt/slides/slide2.xml ---
What is IFD? | International Friendship Day (IFD for short) is a day dedicated to celebrating different cultures of various nationalities. | It encourages people of different nationalities to come together and unite, looking past our differences. | It is actually commemorated on April 10 of 2026

--- ppt/slides/slide3.xml ---
What is our theme for IFD? | The theme is ô | Singapore: Forging friendships in a complex world.ö | A complex world where so many different things are happening, yet we are all able to come together. | Even with all our differences and diversity, we can make friendships with one another.

--- ppt/slides/slide4.xml ---
Our  | ASEAN  | countries | Singapore | Philippines | Vietnam | Malaysia | Indonesia | Myanmar | Laos | Brunei | Thailand | Cambodia | Timor-Leste | (Joined 26 Oct 2025)

--- ppt/slides/slide5.xml ---
Cam | bo | dia | A holiday celebrated in Cambodia: | Khmer New Year (Chaul Chnam Thmey): In April, this is the premier time for strengthening bonds. It is a time for friends and family to gather, exchange gifts, play traditional games, and visit pagodas together. | (1) Traditional dish: | Fish Amok | : A creamy, coconut curry steamed in banana leaves, featuring lemongrass, turmeric, and lime leaves.

--- ppt/slides/slide6.xml ---
Error: 'charmap' codec can't encode character '\u1ebf' in position 50: character maps to <undefined>
